<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root limiter="">
    <HEADER>RADIO X-CEIVER ADMINISTRATION</HEADER>
    <RELEASE>A57</RELEASE>
    <NAME_KEY>MO</NAME_KEY>
    <ACTIVE_KEYS>
        <FAULT_CODES_CLASS_1A in_type="16" out_type="2">
            <b0 index="0"> Radio Unit Fault. Description:
            	The radio unit has indicated an unspecified fault situation.</b0>
            <b1 index="1">HW Fault. Desription:
            The radio unit has indicated it is faulty and it might have to be replaced.</b1>
            <b2 index="2">Software Load of Radio Unit Failed.</b2>
            <b3 index="3">HW and IDB Inconsistent. Description:
            The IDB does not match the RUS/RRUS hardware, for example, wrong frequency band.
Note:
The OMT function Check IDB can be used to identify hardware/IDB inconsistencies.</b3>
            <b4 index="4">Radio Unit in Full Maintenance Mode. Description:
            The RUS/RRUS is in full maintenance mode and cannot be controlled by the BSC.
This can happen, for example, after installing a new IDB.</b4>
        </FAULT_CODES_CLASS_1A>
        <FAULT_CODES_CLASS_1B in_type="16" out_type="2">
            <b0 index="0">Radio Unit Connection Fault.</b0>
            <b1 index="1">Temperature Exceptional.</b1>
            <b2 index="2">Lost Communication to Radio Unit.</b2>
            <b3 index="3">Traffic Lost.</b3>
            <b4 index="4">MSMM/DualDUG Synch Fault.</b4>
            <b5 index="5">Reset, BSC ordered HW Reset. Description:
            The Radio unit is reset with the BSC ordered HW Reset Request Command.
Note:
For information only.</b5>
        </FAULT_CODES_CLASS_1B>
        <FAULT_CODES_CLASS_2A in_type="16" out_type="2">
            <b0 index="0">HW Fault.</b0>
            <b1 index="1">RX Cable Disconnected. Description:
            An RX cable is disconnected or faulty.</b1>
            <b2 index="2">VSWR Over Threshold.</b2>
            <b4 index="4">Temperature Abnormal.</b4>
            <b5 index="5">RX Maxgain Violated.</b5>
            <b6 index="6">Current to high.</b6>
            <b7 index="7">High Frequency of Software Fault. Description:
            Frequent software errors during execution of application software in the RUS/RRUS/AIR/mRRUS.</b7>
            <b8 index="8">Traffic Lost.</b8>
            <b9 index="9">ALNA/TMA Fault.</b9>
            <b10 index="10">Auxiliary Equipment Fault.</b10>
            <b11 index="11">CPRI Delay Too Long Active Path.</b11>
            <b12 index="12">Communication Disturbance Between Radio Units. Description:
            The communication between two RUS/RRUS in a cascade chain is degraded. Probable reason is a high bit error rate.</b12>
            <b13 index="13">Communication Failure Between Radio Units. Description:
            	The RUS/RRUS in a cascade chain has no contact with next RUS/RRUS. A fault indicator is set on the physical layer.</b13>
            <b14 index="14">Communication Equipment Fault in Cascade Chain. Dsecription:
            The RUS/RRUS in a cascade chain has no contact with next RUS/RRUS due to problem with some communication equipment on the radio interface link.</b14>
            <b15 index="15">Lost Communication to Radio Unit in Cascade. Description:
            The RUS/RRUS in a cascade chain has lost communication on the CPRI Link with the next RUS/RRUS.</b15>
            <b16 index="16">RX Path Lost on A Receiver Side. Description:
            	The RX path on the A receiver side of the TRX is lost. This alarm is raised if any related faults are raised on a TRX configured for RX diversity.
If raised on a RU with 4 RF ports and 2 way receiver diversity is enabled, this alarm can be reported on both RF A and RF C.</b16>
            <b17 index="17">RX Path Lost on B Receiver Side. Description:
            The RX path on the B receiver side of the TRX is lost. This alarm is raised if any related faults are raised on a TRX configured for RX diversity.
If raised on a RU with 4 RF ports and 2 way receiver diversity is enabled, this alarm can be reported on both RF B and RF D.</b17>
            <b18 index="18">RX Path Lost on C Receiver Side. Description:
            RX path lost on C receiver side of the TRX is lost. This alarm is raised if any related faults are raised on a TRX configured for 4-way RX diversity.
Note:
This fault is applicable only when 4-way receiver diversity is activated.</b18>
            <b19 index="19">RX Path Lost on D Receiver Side. Description:
            	RX path lost on D receiver side of the TRX is lost. This alarm is raised if any related faults are raised on a TRX configured for 4-way RX diversity.
Note:
This fault is applicable only when 4-way receiver diversity is activated.</b19>
            <b20 index="20">RX Path A Imbalance.</b20>
            <b21 index="21">RX Path B Imbalance.</b21>
            <b22 index="22">RX Path C Imbalance.</b22>
            <b23 index="23">RX Path D Imbalance.</b23>
            <b24 index="24">CPRI Delay Too Long Redundant Path.</b24>
            <b25 index="25">Frequency Bandwidth Mismatch. Description:
            One of the following has occurred in a combined cell:
- The main site and the antenna site do not support the same frequencies

- The extension site supports a narrower frequency bandwidth than the main site</b25>
            <b26 index="26">Tx RF Power Back Off Failed. Description:
            This class 2 alarm indicates that power back off has failed for the reported TX, As a result, the TX has stopped transmitting.</b26>
            <b27 index="27">Feeder Connectivity Fault.</b27>
            <b28 index="28">Lost Communication to Radio Unit.</b28>
            <b29 index="29">AIR Fan Unit Partly Broken(Degraded). Description:
            This alarm indicates that AIR fan unit partially broken, no degradation of the AIR occurs due to redundancy of the fan.
Follow the instructions below until the fault is resolved.

The operator should schedule service within a couple of weeks</b29>
            <b30 index="30">AIR Fan Unit Failure. Description:
            This alarm indicates that AIR fan unit failed. No forced cooling is available in the AIR and dependent on the ambient temperature, severe function degradation may occur.</b30>
            <b31 index="31">AIR fan unit disconnected. Description:
            This alarm indicates that AIR fan unit disconnected. No forced cooling is available in the AIR and dependent on the ambient temperature, severe function degradation may occur.</b31>
            <b32 index="32">Linearization Disturbance Performance Degraded. Description:
            There is a DPD / Linearization fault in the RUS/RRUS.
Please note that without any manual action (see actions below) it will take at least one hour for the alarm to cease.</b32>
        </FAULT_CODES_CLASS_2A>
        <EXTERNAL_FAULT_CODES_CLASS_1 in_type="16" out_type="2">
            <b10 index="10">CC CONF (Inconsistent Combined Cell Configuration).</b10>
        </EXTERNAL_FAULT_CODES_CLASS_1>
    </ACTIVE_KEYS>
    <PRINT_KEYS></PRINT_KEYS>
</root>