<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root limiter="MO\s.*RSLF2\s[\s\S]*?\n{2,}">
    <HEDER>RADIO X-CEIVER ADMINISTRATION MANAGED OBJECT CAPABILITY INFORMATION</HEDER>
    <KEYS>OMLF1 OMLF2 RSLF1</KEYS>
    <NAME_KEY>MO</NAME_KEY>
    <ACTIVE_KEYS limiter="">
        <OMLF1 type="16" start="1,0" end="0,0" norm_val="1">
            <F1 bit="1">TRXC function change not supported by the BTS.</F1>
            <F2 bit="2">Automatic ciphering capability not supported by the BTS.</F2>
            <F3 bit="3">IRC not supported by the BTS.</F3>
            <F4 bit="4">Antenna Hopping not supported by the BTS.</F4>
            <F5 bit="5">Frame Synchronization using GPS not supported by the BTS.</F5>
            <F6 bit="6">4WRD not supported by the BTS.</F6>
            <F7 bit="7">Automatic parameter setting in TG synchronization on TG level not supported by the BTS.</F7>
            <F8 bit="8">Feature Packet Abis over TDM not supported by the BTS.</F8>
            <F9 bit="9">Feature Packet Abis over IP not supported by the BTS.</F9>
            <F10 bit="10">FFTAD not supported by the BTS.</F10>
            <F11 bit="11">PSU Power Savings not supported by the BTS.</F11>
            <F12 bit="12">SC Quality Report II not supported by the BTS.</F12>
            <F13 bit="13">Time Slot Power Savings not supported by the BTS.</F13>
            <F14 bit="14">Multiple CCCH not supported by the BTS.</F14>
            <F15 bit="15">MCTR not supported by the BTS.</F15>
            <F16 bit="16">Current supervised TMA not supported by the BTS.</F16>
            <F17 bit="17">Antenna interface standards group TMA not supported by the BTS.</F17>
            <F18 bit="18">Antenna interface standards group RET not supported by BTS.</F18>
            <F19 bit="19">VAMOS not supported by the BTS.</F19>
            <F20 bit="20">TS configuration split not supported by the BTS.</F20>
            <F21 bit="21">AQPSK with non-zero SCPIR not supported by the BTS.</F21>
            <F22 bit="22">MCTR maximum allowed power extension not supported by the BTS.</F22>
            <F23 bit="23">BCCH Power Savings not supported by the BTS.</F23>
            <F24 bit="24">BTS Soft Synchronization not supported by the BTS.</F24>
            <F25 bit="25">Native IP Configuration not supported by the BTS.</F25>
            <F26 bit="26">RRUS Cascading not supported by the BTS.</F26>
            <F27 bit="27">Reporting of Access Burst Info not supported by the BTS.</F27>
            <F28 bit="28">Decimal resolution of configured power not supported by the BTS.</F28>
            <F29 bit="29">Node Group Synchronization not supported by the BTS.</F29>
            <F30 bit="30">Extended Coverage not supported by the BTS.</F30>
            <F31 bit="31">Synchronization Observability not supported by the BTS.</F31>
        </OMLF1>
        <OMLF2 type="16" start="0,0" end="0,0" norm_val="1">
            <F1 bit="1">Frequency measurements not supported by the BTS.</F1>
        </OMLF2>
        <RSLF1 type="16" start="2,0" end="0,0" norm_val="1">
            <F1 bit="1">Channel Needed not supported.</F1>
            <F2 bit="2">BCCH information phase 2 not supported, Layer 3 (L3) information must be included in Slow
                Associated Control Channel (SACCH) filling, and immediate assign phase 2 not supported.
            </F2>
            <F3 bit="3">Extended range not supported by the BTS.</F3>
            <F4 bit="4">A5/2 algorithm not supported by the BTS.</F4>
            <F5 bit="5">BS power control not supported.</F5>
            <F6 bit="6">Multi-band operation not supported.</F6>
            <F7 bit="7">Power information not supported by the BTS.</F7>
            <F8 bit="8">0A5/1 algorithm not supported by the BTS.</F8>
            <F9 bit="9">GPRS not supported by the BTS.</F9>
            <F10 bit="10">eMLPP priority not supported by the BTS.</F10>
            <F11 bit="11">Extended CBCH not supported by the BTS.</F11>
            <F12 bit="12">Main channel reference not supported.</F12>
            <F13 bit="13">A5/3 algorithm not supported by the BTS.</F13>
            <F14 bit="14">Reporting of BTS Counters not supported by the BTS.</F14>
            <F15 bit="15">IS Connection Point (ICP) List in channel activation not supported.</F15>
            <F16 bit="16">EMR functionality not supported by the BTS.</F16>
            <F17 bit="17">TFO not supported.</F17>
            <F18 bit="18">VGCS not supported by the BTS.</F18>
            <F19 bit="19">VGCS Enhancements not supported by the BTS.</F19>
            <F20 bit="20">FFAD not supported by the BTS.</F20>
            <F21 bit="21">Enhanced Handover Success Rate not supported by the BTS.</F21>
            <F22 bit="22">Repeated SACCH not supported by the BTS.</F22>
            <F23 bit="23">RTTI not supported by the BTS.</F23>
            <F24 bit="24">PTA regulation algorithm 1 not supported by the BTS.</F24>
            <F25 bit="25">PAN not supported by the BTS.</F25>
            <F26 bit="26">Random fill bits not supported by the BTS.</F26>
            <F27 bit="27">BS Power 2 not supported by the BTS.</F27>
            <F28 bit="28">DRX mode not supported by the BTS.</F28>
            <F29 bit="29">0VAMOS enhancements in BSC G12B release not supported by the BTS.</F29>
            <F30 bit="30">Packet Data Channel (PDCH) options not supported by the BTS.</F30>
            <F31 bit="31">Random SI6 fill bits not supported by the BTS.</F31>
            <F32 bit="32">Channel Specific MI not supported.</F32>
            <F34 bit="34">A5/4 algorithm not supported by the BTS.</F34>
            <F35 bit="35">Extended Coverage not supported by the BTS.</F35>
            <F36 bit="36">Extended DRX not supported by the BTS.</F36>
        </RSLF1>
    </ACTIVE_KEYS>
    <!--all keys that should print beside active keys/ active keys should not be here-->
    <PRINT_KEYS></PRINT_KEYS>
</root>



